long time no see.
久しぶり
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
How have you been?
元気してた?
You're cute, smiling as always.
可愛いね、笑顔、相変わらずね
With that smile, recently a man
その笑顔で、最近男
...
Well then, the other day...
じゃあ さ、この前さ、
Last time, I didn't really listen to it, so
前 回さ、あんまり聞けなかったから、
It's a little naughty.
ちょっとさ、エッチなことさ
Do you like sex?
エッチ好き?
I like it.
好きだね
I like this.
これ好きだね
I like it when you don't answer right away.
即答しないと好きだね
You don't hate it, though.
嫌じゃないでしょ、でも
Which one do you prefer?
どっちかってと好きなの
Totally fine.
全然いい
It's okay though, it's cute.
全然いいんじゃ可愛いけどね
How do you like sex?
どうエッチが好き?
For example, situations.
例えば、シチュエーションとか
Situations, for example...
シチュエーション、例えば...
For example, do you like SM music?
プレイというか、例えばSM系が好きなのか、
My boyfriend's house balcony
彼氏の家のベランダとか、
It's like they took away the treatment for my stomach.
腹 の処置を奪っちゃったみたいな
Isn't that why you want to have sex in such a strange way?
だから、そういう変わってエッチしたいなとかないの?
Cold storm.
寒暴
So what are you going to say?
じゃあ、何か言うの?
Are you being vague?
漠然としてるの?
It would be nice if you would like to play the leading role once in a while.
どっちかたまには、 主役的なこともしたいみたいなのがいいね
My Sth time, etc.
自分S回目とか、
Can't you live kindly?
優 しく住めない?
I'm a bit of an old man, so I have some jokes.
ちょっとおじさんだからさ、 ジョークあるんだけどさ、
It turned out to be the opposite.
逆がい物になったわ
Have you had a hefrah recently?
最近ヘフラした?
A dick other than mine?
俺以外のチンコ?
Aren't you huffing?
ヘフラしてない?
Do you ever feel horny?
ムラムラするときってあるの?
You said you didn't have sex, right?
エッチしてないって言ってたじゃん?
Don't you feel horny?
ムラムラとかしないの?
Were you horny and alone?
ムラムラして一人でしたの?
what are you doing?
何してるの?
What do you do alone?
一人で何するの?
What was I supposed to do alone?
一人で何したはず?
So cute, so embarrassing.
かわいいね、恥ずかしい
Don't use toys?
おもちゃも使わない?
If you ask a woman, is she in the middle of Kurihara?
女に言えばさ、 クリハラの中腹の?
Why are you here?
なんでここにいるの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
How much Shu?
シュウどれぐらい?
How often?
どれぐらいの頻度にするの?
So what if Shu gets horny twice?
じゃあシュウ2回ムラムラすると?
Well then, you had sex with me last time, right?
じゃあさ、前回俺とエッチしたじゃん?
I had sex.
エッチしたよ
There were girls who wanted to have sex, and there were men who had sex.
エッチしたい子ってか、 エッチした男が現れてた
I already called you on my own.
もう、勝手に呼んじゃったんだけど
I'm calling you.
呼んでるんだけど
I'm surprised.
びっくりしてる
Touch my dick, it's amazing, something like that
ちんこ触って、すごいちん、なんか
I'm looking at your pants.
パ ンツ見てる
A man who is dying to have sex,
エッチしたくてたまんない男がさ、
I feel comfortable.
心地もできてる
Let's take a deep breath and calm down.
ちょっと深呼吸して整えようか
Fee fee fee Let's take a deep breath and calm down.
フ ィーフィーフィー 深呼吸して整えよう
Let's calm down.
緊張整えよう
Let's go, then.
行くよ、じゃあ
I'll call you.
呼んじゃうよ
I'll call others too.
他にも呼びますね
Let them take the lead.
リードしてもらう
You remember.
覚えてるんですね
That's amazing.
すごいっすね
You're beautiful, aren't you?
綺麗っすね、お前
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
恥 ず か しい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Ah, I guess I'll have to push it a bit.
あ、なんかちょっと若干 手押すかね
I'll do it even if I feel like it.
気まんでもするね
Fluttering, toys after all.
ひらひらし、おもちゃやっぱ
sorry.
すみません
Please take a break.
ゆっくり休憩してください
Please push again.
もう 一 度、手押ししてください
Please press your hand again.
もう一度、手押ししてください
Ai, ai, ku,
あいっ、あいっ、 くっ、
It felt good.
気 持ちよかった